[{"id": 600, "question": "STRANGERS parties go wild these days. The main idea of them is to never let the people know who their matches are until the last minute. These are some popular practices that are storming the world's youth on this V-day. Speed dating It's exactly what the name implies. Complete with a timer, a whistle and 50 willing singles, speed dating is not the traditional dinner and a movie type of first date. Singles pay US $35 for three minutes with more than two dozen future dates. They ask questions and try to get to know each other. At the sound of a whistle, they do the same thing all over again--25 times in all. Lock and key party Women are given a lock and men are given a key, upon arriving at the party. Each key and lock has several matches. One can hunt for his/her later-to-be sweetheart in ...\n\nQ: What do you think the similarities of these parties are?", "options": ["All the parties have very strict rules for their members.", "If you want to go to any of the parties, you have to buy a ticket.", "All the parties are aimed at strangers who want to be lovers.", "All the parties are suitable not only for the young but for the old."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2598, "question": "Chinese President Hu Jintao, on his way to talks with President George W. Bush in prefix = st1 /Washington, on Tuesday met with Bill Gates. After the meeting with Gates, the world's richest man, at Microsoft's headquarters, Hu restated that China would move against software pirates all the time. At Microsoft Corp.'s campus, Hu said on Tuesday he admired what Microsoft Chairman Bill Gates had achieved. He also sought to reassure Gates that China is serious about protecting intellectual property rights . \"Because you, Mr. Bill Gates, are a friend of China, I'm a friend of Microsoft,\" Hu said. \"Also, I am dealing with the operating system produced by Microsoft every day,\" he added, to laughter. Gates responded: \"Thank you, it's a fantastic relationship,\" and then said: \"And if you ever need a...\n\nQ: How many issues are mentioned in President Hu's visit to Microsoft?", "options": ["One.", "Two.", "Three.", "Four."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2088, "question": "Hair has always been an important sign of beauty, especially true for women.Next to the face, hair is one of the main qualities people look for when they consider a woman's beauty.Whether long or short, curly or straight, hair often gets a lot of attention. Each hair grows independently of other hairs.Not all hairs experience the same period of growth at the same time.During the period of active growth, which is called Anagen, hair grows at a rate of about or one centimeter a month.About eighty five percent of hair follicles are going through this process at any given time.This period can last from two to six years. The Catagen period of hair growth comes next.It is then that hair growth begins to slow down.This period usually lasts two or three weeks.Finally, hair growth comes to a comple...\n\nQ: What is suggested by health experts when one suffers from a sudden increase in hair loss?", "options": ["Changing his genes.", "Going to see a doctor.", "Cutting all his hair off.", "Eating more vegetables."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1508, "question": "Since my son is getting ready for first grade, I asked a friend where she shops for school supplies. For price and convenience, she had a quick answer: schoolpak.com. Parents can buy items or packaged equipment for all grades. The Generic Elementary School-pak for first through fifth graders, for example, is $23.28. (Teachers can also e-mail their grade's or school's whole list for a price on customized kits . Shipping is free for 75 or more kits) _ Teachers thinks highly of educationalwarehouse.com for its learning tools and games--everything from puzzles and puppets to software and chalks.Classroomdirect.com has great prices on over 10.000 products and a special corner offering even deeper discounts. Pick your lunch box The second-most-difficult back-to-school decision, right after what ...\n\nQ: What does the writer think of picking a lunch box?", "options": ["It is very easy", "It is rather hard", "It proves interesting", "It seems special"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3364, "question": "\"Hitler and the Germans,\" an exhibition in Berlin's German Historical Museum which aims to investigate the society that created Hitler, has seen more than 10,000 visitors walk through its doors since opening on Friday. Rudolf Trabold, a spokesman for the museum, said there were 4,000 visitors to the exhibition on the first day alone. People visiting the exhibition said they had waited as long as one and a half hours to get in. Ravi Nair, a 73-year-old Indian visitor, said: \"I had to queue for about an hour but it was worth it. The exhibition should help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable.\" Trabold said \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because it was the first exhibition to explain how a man who lived on the margins of society for 30 years, in Vie...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the passage?", "options": ["The visitors coming to \"Hitler and the Germans\" are all old people.", "\"Hitler and the Germans\" has made an impression on every visitor.", "Some neo-Nazi admirers of Hitler have caused a lot of trouble.", "People visit \"Hitler and the Germans\" with variety of purposes."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1502, "question": "Columbus made four voyages to the west between 1492 and 1504 in his vain search for a sea route to Asia. The mystery of why he failed to find it haunted him and filled him with sadness. Wherever he went to Cuba, Puerto Rico, Jamaica, South America, Panama, down the coast of Central America--it was always the same story. Instead of golden palaces, there were grass huts and palm-leaf tents. Instead of silk-robed merchant princes, he found \"Indians\" who did not have so much as a shirt on their backs. When Columbus explored the West Indies in 1493,he heard tales of a fierce Indian tribe who literally devoured its defeated enemies after a battle. These people were called by many names in the area, including Calina, Canima, Carib, and Caniba. Columbus recorded the name of the American natives as...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this text?", "options": ["Sailing to Asia", "Columbus' voyages", "West Indies", "Spice Islands"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 545, "question": "Yueyang Tower lies in the west of Yueyang City, near the Dongting Lake. It was first built for soldiers to rest on and watch out. In the Three Kingdoms Period, Lu Su, General of Wu State, trained his soldiers here. In 716, Kaiyuan of Tang Dynasty, General Zhang Shuo was sent to defend at Yuezhou and he rebuilt it into a tower named South Tower, and then Yueyang Tower. In 1044, Song Dynasty, Teng Zijing was stationed at Baling Jun, the ancient name of Yueyang City. In the second year, he had the Yueyang Tower repaired and had poems by famous poets written on the walls of the tower. Fan Zhongyan, a great artist and poet, was invited to write the well-known poem about Yueyang Tower. In his A Panegyric of the Yueyang Tower (<<>> ), Fan writes: \"Be the first to worry about the troubles across t...\n\nQ: Which of the following has nothing to do with Yueyang Tower?", "options": ["Huaifu Pavilion.", "Xiaoxiang Door.", "Tomb of Du Fu.", "Tomb of Xiaoqiao."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1679, "question": "The round-the-clock availability that cell phones have brought to people's lives may be _ amily life, a new study suggests. The study, which followed more than 1300 adults over 2 years, found that those who consistently used a mobile phone through out the study period were more likely to report negative \"spillover\" between work and home life--and, in turn, less satisfaction with their family life. Spillover(,) actually means that the line between work and home began to become unclear. Work life may invade home life--when a parent is taking job-related calls at home, for instance--or family issues may start to take up work time. For example, a child may call Mom at work, telling her \"the microwave exploded\", explained Noelle Chesley, an assistant professor of society at the University of Wi...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["Cell phones offer 24-hour availability.", "Cell phones get life and work mixed.", "Women don't use cell phones in an effective way.", "Men are better at dealing with family problems."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2205, "question": "The picture-like island is rich in scenic beauty. Barbados sightseeing is a photographer's dream that comes true with numbers of natural wonders, breathtaking scenic views, attractive gardens and miles of white, sandy beaches. There's so many things to see and to do, as you check out some of the places of interest on the island. Historical Appeal Experience Full of historical appeal you'll love the impressive collection of beautiful great houses, landmarks, old churches, and traditional ancient houses some of which may date back to the 16th century. Historic Bridgetown, over 375 years old, capital of Barbados, is located with its color1ful fishing boats and splendid yachts ( ) . Check out the Barbados National and see some of the island's most beautiful homes. Nature Charm Enjoyment Nature...\n\nQ: According to the passage Botanical Garden   _", "options": ["can make tours dangerous with rocky caves", "is full of tropical plants and landmarks", "will cost travelers lots of money", "may attract lovers of nature"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2946, "question": "Johnson went to Penquay for the weekend. He arrived there late on Friday evening. The landlady of the guest house, Mrs. Smith, answered the door and showed him to his room. Johnson was very tired and went straight to bed. He slept well and didn't wake up until nine o'clock the next morning. Johnson went downstairs for breakfast. Because there were no other guests, Mrs. Smith invited him to have breakfast with her family. Her only daughter, Catherine, about 13, was already sitting in the dining-room. Mrs. Smith went to the kitchen to prepare breakfast. Johnson noticed there were four places at the table and asked Catherine if there was another guest. Catherine told him that it was an empty place. And it used to be her father's place. Her father had been a fisherman. Three years before he ha...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Catherine's father got lost on the sea.", "Mrs. Smith does not love her husband.", "Johnson may be killed by the man.", "Catherine is fond of telling stories."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 531, "question": "A new study warns that about thirty percent of the world's people may not have enough water by the year 2025. An American organization called Population Action International did the new study. It was more than three hundred and thirty-five million people lack enough water now. The people live in twenty-eight countries. Most of the countries are in Africa or in the Middle East. Population Action International researcher Robert Engelman says by the year 2025, about three thousand million people lack water. At least 18 more countries are expected to have serious water problems. The demand for water keeps increasing. Yet the amount of water on the earth the same. Mr Engelman says the population in countries that lack water is growing in these countries will continue to increase. The report say...\n\nQ: _    million will lack water by the year 2025?", "options": ["335", "3,000", "3,305", "355"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1655, "question": "Do you love Beats headphones, True Religion jeans, and UGG shoes? These are some of the most popular brands around. They are also expensive. But some experts say they are not much better than cheaper brands. For example, Jim Wilcox works for Consumer Reports. He tested all kinds of headphones. He says that $80 Koss Pro headphones provide basically the same quality and comfort as Beats. So why do people pay twice or even 10 times as much for the hottest brands? Experts say it's because fashionable, expensive brands send a message. Brands say \"I belong\" or \"I can afford it.\" Some people think that expensive brand names are worth the price. They say that some designer clothes really are top quality and that they last longer than cheaper brands. Some teenagers choose to wear popular brands bec...\n\nQ: The text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["how to buy things reasonably", "the competition between brands", "the different values of teenagers", "whether expensive brands are worth high prices"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 838, "question": "Scholarship Application Tips in 2014 for college students *Before you apply 1. Work hard to get good grades. Don't sweat about one bad grade, but always strive to do your best. 2. Get involved, and stay involved, in extracurricular activities. Sports, clubs, drama, bands and orchestras-these often count toward a student's overall scholarship application evaluation. The same goes for paid (or unpaid) work experience. 3. Begin your scholarship research early-by your sophomore or junior year of high school, if possible. Make special note of application deadlines, as they can vary from late summer to late spring. 4. Apply for as many scholarships as you are eligible for-several smaller scholarships can add up to a lot of money. *During the application process 1. Read the supplementary material...\n\nQ: The author suggests that applicants should  _  .", "options": ["submit the application in the few days", "double-check their application with their parents", "complete and submit the application in one day", "avoid submitting the application online"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1215, "question": "A number of times Rosemary edged closer to Gordon , meaning to take his arm, but he edged away from her. She thought that she had offended him deeply, and that he was disappointed because she had pushed him away. She would have apologized if he had given her half a chance. But as a matter of fact, he was scarcely thinking of this any longer. It was the money business that was troubling him now. And the fact was that he would soon have to confess it. What nonsense it made of all he had said! Presently she stopped him, and swung him round to face her. \"Gordon, why won't you speak to me?\" she said. \"Are you still angry with me for what happened just now?\" \"No, I was never angry with you. You're not to blame. Something else has been worrying me all the way along, I've only eight pence left. I ...\n\nQ: Gordon felt that if he asked rosemary to lend him some money    _   .", "options": ["he would lose some of his self-respect", "she would refuse to", "he would have to confess his loss", "she would be angry"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1461, "question": "When, after a year of being alone on his island, Robinson Crusoe sees a footprint in the sand, the reader of Robinson Crusoe trembles. Will Crusoe find another human being to end his loneliness? Is the footprint the sign of an enemy? Since 1719, when Daniel Defoe wrote Robinson Crusoe, thousands of people who enjoy English novels have thrilled to this great adventure story. But few know how the story came to be written. Robinson Crusoe was the first English novel. Its birth brought together the misadventures of a Scotch \"failure\" and the untapped imagination of an aging English scribbler. Near the end of the Seventeenth Century, the hot-tempered Alexander Selkirk was charged with bad conduct while in church. Rather than face this charge, he ran away to sea. Several years later, Selkirk fou...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards Daniel Defoe is_.", "options": ["critical", "supporting", "both A and B", "opposing"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2157, "question": "The Haitian tsunami gave scientists a chance to find out how well vital and potentially life-saving warning systems were working. Noaa's Pacific Marine Environmental Laboratory has developed a warning system that picks up signals of tsunamis directly from the sea-floor. It is called Dart-the Deep-ocean Assessment and Reporting of Tsunamis. If seismometers detect an earthquake, the Dart buoys will determine what is happening to sea levels, and whether a big wave might be on the way. This information is then sent via satellite to a central location which can organize an alarm. Within 50 minutes of the Haiti earthquake, this system was able to issue an alarm to other countries in the Caribbean to say that a small tsunami had been caused to start, and that was unlikely to affect them. Dr Berna...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Tsunami Assessment", "Earthquake detecting", "Disaster Warning System", "Life Saving System"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 489, "question": "WILD WEATHERMAN Name: Sam Champion Hot job: TV Weatherman Where: ABC-TV, New York City When you were a child, did you plan to forecast wind, rain, and snow on TV? I wanted to be a foreign journalist. I took courses in weather science at Eastern Kentucky University, but I majored in broadcasting news. How did you finally become a weatherman? My first job in the early 1980s was at the local TV station in Paducah, Kentucky. I did everything from turning on the lights in the morning to writing and delivering morning news. I put together weather forecasts, and became interested in them. Back then, how did you forecast weather? Independent companies collected computer information that showed, for example, how a single weather system might split into snow or snow mixed with rain. The information ...\n\nQ: Judging from the writing style, the text is    _   .", "options": ["a diary", "an interview", "a news story", "an announcement"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1151, "question": "Downing the last drop of an expensive famous brand H2O as well as remembering to throw the empty bottle in the recycling bin, makes you feel pretty good about yourself, _ Even when the bottles are recycles, there are all kinds of other consequences of swallowing bottled water, says Melissa Peffers, the air-quality program manager for Environmental Defense. The containers are often filled in faraway lands, then shipped from abroad, and stored in refrigerators at your local store. Compare that with the influence on environment of turning on your tap, filling a glass, and drinking up! Anyone who is choosing bottled water for health reasons is misguided, says Peffers, \"Most bottled water is just tap water.\" And what comes out of your tap is carefully monitored to follow the strict rules. Consi...\n\nQ: According to the author, tap water is_.", "options": ["as safe as bottled water", "more likely to be polluted", "healthier than bottled water", "less convenient than bottled water"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3395, "question": "Since the 1950s, most of the stars of pop music have come from Britain and America. Howver, in the last ten years, when many different kinds of music have established themselves on the pop scene, more and more stars have come from other countries. Pop music changes all the time and new stars appear and become famous. For a musician to stay popular and still produced good, original music over a long period of time, is a sign of true star. Most stars start their careers in a simple way---- playing in unknown night clubs or dance-hall where people want to dance to the music, not listen to it. They may have continued doing this for many years untill they get a \"break\"---- a chance to perform in a well -known place or get a recording contract. To become a star is the aim of every singer or musi...\n\nQ: If a star becomes successful,.he   _   according to the passage.", "options": ["will live at home with their parents", "will have an easy life because of the larger amount of money earned", "may have a happy home life and good person relationships", "may have a lonely life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2891, "question": "From Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou, you can travel along the East Line not only the other line going past Dujiangyan and Wenchuan. Take a regular bus from Chengdu Chengbei Bus Station from 9:00 to 16:30. It only takes about three hours to Jiangyou. The ticket is CNY50.00 net per person. Up along Fujiang River, you will pass the second largest city in Sichuan, Mianyang and enjoy the picturesque scenery. There is bus available to the destination from 6:30 to 13:30 in Mianyang Pingzheng Bus Station,The one way ticket is about CNY95.00 net per person. In this case, you can not get stop at Jiangyou and Pingwu. This is one option for you. In Jiangyou, visit the Former Residence of Li Bai, the famous poet in Tang Dynasty. If time permits, you can also take a look at the Doutuan Mountain, which is famous ...\n\nQ: What is the tour route of the East Line from Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou according to the passage?", "options": ["Chengdu - Mianyang - Jiangyou - Huanglong - Pingwu - Chuanzhusi - Jiuzhaigou", "Chengdu - Mianyang - Fujiang - Jiangyou - Pingwu - Huanglong - Jiuzhaigou", "Chengdu - Mianyang - Jiangyou - Pingwu - Huanglong - Chuanzhusi - Jiuzhaigou", "Chengdu - Mianyang - Jiangyou - Pingwu - Chuanzhusi-Huanglong - Jiuzhaigou"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3257, "question": "Teachers and textbooks _ -- your future could be under threat from a quickly developing and very smart technology. University of California researchers led by Jacob White hill recently programmed teaching robots to react to facial expression. Whitehill's achievement marked a major step forward in the way people could one day learn by establishing facial expression recognition in robot teachers. The teaching robots or, Intelligent Tutoring Systems (ITS) are computer systems that provide personalized instruction and feedback to students without human intervention. The facial expression recognition allows a computer to react according to expressions a user makes. He said that the system was an important development in improving learning systems. \"Classical ITS typically have a somewhat rigid ...\n\nQ: The author wrote the passage aiming to", "options": ["warn teachers against robot teachers in advance", "explain how robot teachers in the future work", "introduce a newly developed teaching robot", "show his respect for the designers of the advanced ITS"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2283, "question": "Where can you find a nice place to relax on holiday for both you and your children? Well, I suggest you try the beautiful and green Isle of Wight (IOW). The Isle of Wight is one of the main tourist attractions. Here is some information on a few of the attractions on the IOW. Dinosaur Isle It is located in Sandown, a seaside town on the southeast coast. It's a large, lovely museum, both fun and educational. Here you can see a large fossil collection of all kinds of dinosaurs, as well as a gift shop. You can walk into the past and then the future, learning about the history and the development of the civilization of dinosaurs that lived 120 million years ago. Robin Hill Country Park The park is in the beautiful countryside, and is suitable for children's parties and games. It has five new ga...\n\nQ: The purpose of this passage is to   _  .", "options": ["show the development of tourism on the IOW", "tell readers what is worth visiting", "attract readers to come to the IOW", "advise readers how to relax on holidays"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1905, "question": "If you want to live longer and lower the risk of heart disease, a move to the mountains may help. Research by scientists in Greece shows that living in the mountains is good for the heart and longevity . People living at higher altitude have lower possibility of dying from heart disease than those closer to sea level, even if they have factors that could increase their risk. \"Residence in mountainous areas seems to have a 'protective effect' from heart disease,\" said Dr Nikos Baibas of the University of Athens. He and his colleagues suspect that the increased exercise from walking up mountainous area gives the heart a good workout and enables it to cope with lower levels of oxygen. Researchers studied the health records and death rates of 1,150 Greeks who lived in three villages near Athen...\n\nQ: According to the passage, a person   _   may have less possibility of having heart attack.", "options": ["from higher altitude", "with a better living habit", "with more money", "in a happier mood"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2922, "question": "British MPs have voted in favour of the creation of babies with DNA from two women and one man, in a historic move. The UK is now set to become the first country to introduce laws to allow the creation of babies from three people. In a free vote in the Commons, 382 MPs were in favour and 128 against the technique that stops genetic diseases being passed from mother to child. During the debate, ministers said the technique was \"light at the end of a dark tunnel\" for families. A further vote is required in the House of Lords. If everything goes ahead then the first such baby could be born next year. Supporters said it was \"good news for progressive medicine\" but critics say they will continue to fight against the technique that they say raises too many ethical and safety concerns. Estimates ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["Mitochondria are inside nearly every cell that change food into useable energy", "DNA of Mitochondria can affect a person's appearance", "in medical science ethical factors should be taken into consideration", "the donor woman's DNA will not be found in the three-person baby"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2139, "question": "Many kids don't drink enough water daily, according to a new study. The study's lead author, Erica Kenney, at first planned to look into the amount of sugary drinks kids were drinking in schools. However, during her research she found that many kids were simply not drinking enough water. Kenney and her team examined data from a group of 4,000 children, aged 6 to19, between the years of 2009 and 2012. The data was taken from the National Health and Nutrition Survey,a study on the health of children in the United States conducted each year by the Center for Disease Control and Prevention.. While looking through the survey results, she noticed that more than half of the kids who took part in the study were dehydrated . Of' that group, boys were 76% more likely than girls not to have enough wa...\n\nQ: According to the findings of Erica Kenney's study, we know that   _  .", "options": ["school kids cannot find drinkable water easily", "boys are more likely to get dehydrated than girls", "sugary drinks are very popular with school kids", "most kids know the importance of drinking plain water ."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2990, "question": "Hidden in a small street in the south end of Springfield, not far from buildings torn apart by the tornado earlier this year, Frigo's is an Italian restaurant right in our own backyard. Frigo's is not a tiny place. It provides different kinds of Italian food. There are refrigerator cases full of prepared foods and desserts, and shelves filled with olives and various pasta. There's some traditional Italian music and the smell is of olive oil and garlic . Above the largest refrigerator case, there's a chalk board covered with desriptions of more Italian sandwiches than I could remember. I stepped into Frigo's almost by accident when I had to stay in Springfield into the evening for an open house at the school where I work. Frigo's is the perfect place to find something quick to go. There are...\n\nQ: We can infer that \"Joe's Favorite\" and \"Dante\" are the names of  _  .", "options": ["sandwiches", "salads", "cheese", "peppers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2360, "question": "The crowd cheered and cheered. The man with the horn waved and smiled his great smile. \"More! More!\" cried the crowd. And Louis Armstrong took his horn and began to play again. Here he was in England. Now a famous man, he was rich. He knew many important people. Wherever he went, people knew his name. They wanted to hear his music. As he played the sad, slow songs, Louis thought of his home in New Orleans. He lived there as a boy. It was a busy, exciting city. But Louis's family was very poor. He went to work to help his mother. He also went to school. One of Louis's teachers asked him to join the school band. \"This horn is yours until you leave our school,\" his teacher said. Louis's music was jazz and he loved it. He remembered all the music he heard. He didn't learn to read music until h...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for this story ?.", "options": ["Musician", "A beautiful horn", "Sweet smiles", "The man with the horn"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1020, "question": "A group of graduates, well established in their careers, were talking at a reunion and decided to visit their old university professor, now retired. During their visit, the conversation turned to complaints about stress in their work and lives. Offering his guests hot chocolate, the professor went into the kitchen and returned with a large pot of hot chocolate and other things including cups-porcelain , glass, crystal, some plain looking, some expensive, some elegant -- telling them to help themselves to the hot chocolate. When they all had a cup of hot chocolate in hand, the professor said: \"I notice that all the nice looking and expensive cups were taken, leaving behind the plain and cheap ones. While it is normal for you to want only the best for yourselves, that is the source of your p...\n\nQ: What does the word \"cup\" in this passage refer to?", "options": ["Life", "happy things in life", "hot chocolate", "tools to hold and contain life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1196, "question": "Harvard researchers have created a tough, low-cost, biodegradable material inspired by insects' hard outer shells. The material's inventors say it has a number of possible uses and someday could provide a more environmentally friendly alternative to plastic. The material, made from shrimp (') shells and proteins produced from silk, is called \"shrilk.\" It is thin, clear, flexible and strong. A major benefit of the material is its biodegradability. Plastic's toughness and flexibility represented a revolution in materials science during the 1950s and '60s. Decades later, however, plastic's very durability is raising questions about how appropriate it is for one-time products such as plastic bags, or short-lived consumer goods, used in the home for a few years and then cast into a landfill whe...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Recent Progress in Environmental Protection", "Benefits of Insects in Scientific Research", "The Harm of One-time Products", "A Possible Alternative to Plastic"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2821, "question": "When someone meets a stranger with the same hobby, that person immediately becomes a friend. People enjoy the company of others who share a similar interest. Often they will form a club and travel great distances to attend meetings where they can talk about their hobbies. Other people have such unusual hobbies that no one else can share them. Sometimes they try to do something better, faster or longer than anyone else in order to have their names included in the Guinness Book of World Records. A lady in Massachusetts may have the world's easiest hobby; she let her hair grow. Diane Witt has not cut her hair for twelve years. It is now eight feet (2.44 meters) long, and she will soon set a new world record and her name will be placed in the Guinness Book. A thirty-year-old man in Pennsylvani...\n\nQ: Judging from the writing style of the passage, it is   _  .", "options": ["a piece of advertisement", "a science report", "a passage for professional reading", "a passage from a magazine"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1199, "question": "It is under the CPC's leadership that China has overcome many challenges in its economic, political and social systems and achieved remarkable progress the world has ever seen. Under the CPC's leadership, China has become the world's largest second largest economy. People's lives have greatly improved, and hundreds of millions of people have been lifted out of poverty, an objective fact no one can deny. At the same time, China is quickly becoming a major player on the world stage. As a responsible nation, China has been playing a growing role and shouldered greater responsibilities in world affairs. Such achievements, especially for a nation with a size equaling to a continent and a population of nearly 1.4 billion, are not easy to make. What roles do you think CPC has played in China? Do ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, CPC refers to_.", "options": ["Communist Party of China", "Cost Per Click", "card-programming control", "Computer Process Control"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 243, "question": "As many people hit middle age, they often start to notice that their memory and mental attention are not what they used to be. We suddenly can't remember where we put the keys just a moment ago, or an old friend's name, or the name of an old band we used to love. It happens to most of us, but is it unavoidable? Scientists are increasingly showing that there's actually a lot that can be done. It turns that the brain needs exercise in much the same way as our muscles do, and the right mental workouts can improve our basic cognitive functions. Now, a new San Francisco Web-based company has taken it a step further and developed the first \"brain training program\" designed to actually help people improve and regain their mental sharpness. Called Lumosity, it was designed by some of the leading e...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?", "options": ["Memory losing is unavoidable.", "Lumosity is unreasonable.", "Muscles don't need exercise.", "Brains need exercise."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 748, "question": "We do not know when man first began to use salt, but we do know that it has been used in many different ways throughout history. Historical evidence shows, for example, that people who lived over 3,000 years ago ate salted fish. Thousands of years ago in Egypt, salt was used to preserve the dead. Stealing salt was considered a major crime during some periods of history. In the eighteenth century, for example, if a person was caught stealing salt, he could be put in prison and his ears could be cut off. In the Roman Empire, one of the most important roads was the one that carried salt from the salt mines to Rome. Guards were stationed along the route to protect against salt thieves, and they received their pay in salt, thus bringing the English word, salary. Any guard who fell asleep while ...\n\nQ: In the Roman Empire many people were employed as guards to   _  .", "options": ["protect the city of Rome", "watch people carrying salt", "prevent thieves from stealing salt", "carry salt from the mines to Rome"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2827, "question": "Are you the kind of person who likes staying in unusual places? If the answer is \"yes\", then try the world's coldest hotel in Jukkasjarvi in the north of Sweden. But go in winter to all you'll find is a pool of water, because the hotel melts every spring! The man who runs the Artic Hall Hotel is Nils Yngve Bergqvist. He built his first ice building for an art exhibition in 1991 and he designed the present hotel-over 200 meters square-himself. It took workmen about two months to pile 1,000 tons of snow onto a wooden base. As the weather got colder, the snow froze and then they removed the base. The whole building and everything in it are made of snow-except for the wooden front door. There's a theatre which Nils uses for a jazz club, a radio station and a large ice bar. As you can imagine, ...\n\nQ: Nils uses the theatre for    _  .", "options": ["abc", "bcd", "abd", "acd"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2405, "question": "Another of President Bush's critics on climate change and his former rival for the White House, Al Gore, is inprefix = st1 /Londonon Friday to launch an environmental project with the head of the Virgin Business Company, Richard Branson. They're announcing a multi-million dollar international prize to encourage development and research into new forms of low carbon technology. The prize will be available to anyone who can apply a successful method of removing large amounts of carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Almost all scientists agree that we are experiencing global warming due to increased amounts of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. Carbon dioxide is released when fuel is burned. Oil, coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas. When biological wasted breaks down, it also release...\n\nQ: People would like to remove carbon dioxide from the atmosphere, but they don't like the method of_.", "options": ["compressing it and pumping it into the ground", "burning the fossil fuel", "pumping it into the atmosphere.", "reducing too much fossil fuel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3084, "question": "Wild animals seem to have escaped the Indian Ocean tsunami , adding weight to ideas they possess a \"sixth sense\" for disasters, experts said on Thursday. Sri Lanka wildlife officials have said the giant waves that killed over 24,000 people along the Indian Ocean island's coast seemingly missed wild beasts, with no dead animals found. \"No elephants are dead, not even a dead hare or rabbit. I think animals can sense disaster. They have a sixth sense. They know when things are happening,\" H.D. Ratnayake, deputy director of Sri Lanka's Wildlife Department, said on Wednesday. The waves washed floodwaters up to 3 km (2 miles) inland at Yala National Park in the southeast, Sri Lanka's biggest wildlife reserve and home to hundreds of wild elephants. \"There has been a lot of evidence about dogs bar...\n\nQ: What does the term \"sixth sense\" in the text means?", "options": ["It is the natural ability of animals that can save them from danger.", "It is the animal's imagination in the brain.", "It is some hidden power to say in advance that something will happen.", "It is a kind of sense that is the same as smell or hearing."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 348, "question": "Taichi with English narration A veteran Taichi teacher, about 38, teaches the basic 24 movements, pushinghands and self-defense techniques, suitable for the beginners and intermediate level. Time:10:00-12:00 a.m., every Sunday morning Place: Bamboo Garden Hotel, No 24, Xiaoshiqiao Hutong, jiuprefix = st1 /Gulou Street, Northwestof Drum Tower in the downtown. Fee: 60 yuan each time Chinese ink & water painting class To learn the techniques of painting a bird, flower, or lady with brushes. The Chinese philosophy and culture will also be included Time: 7:00-9:00p.m. every Wednesday Place: Library Bar, first floor, Tower B of East Gate Plaza ,right behind the poly plaza at the East Second Ring Road. Fee: 60 yuan each week Big-bowl-tea Ten yuan (US$1.2) for a cup of Chinese tea and live perform...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOTtrue?", "options": ["You can enjoy acrobatic shows every day at 7 p.m. in the open air.", "You can see live performance of Peking Opera while enjoying Chinese traditional tea", "You don't have to worry about the language problem to attend Taichi if you are an Englishman", "Chinese ink &water painting class is probably open to learner from outside China"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3055, "question": "One warm September night, Mira had come down to the beach to enjoy the night air. She closed her eyes and listened to the waves. Suddenly, she could hear another sound, so she opened her eyes and looked down at the sand. It was moving! All of a sudden she could see a tiny head coming out. Then a turtle appeared! One by one they struggled out of their underground nests. Mira looked in surprise at the baby turtles. Mira knew the turtles should head towards the waves and swim away, so she was puzzled when they began to pull themselves towards the dunes . Suddenly, she remembered something her grandmother had told her. \"Sea turtles bury their eggs on the beach every year in April and in September. Those baby turtles hatch and head back down to the sea. But some of them never make it. Sometimes...\n\nQ: This story is mainly about a girl   _  .", "options": ["enjoying the ocean", "turning lights off at night", "saving the baby turtles", "learning from her grandparents"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1150, "question": "Planning to go to a gym? If you are one of those who have spent many days planning to join a gym or to attend it regularly, then why not choose some home exercise? Here are some home exercises without equipment. Jumping jacks This one is the best home workout without weights which is a great exercise that will work your hands and legs. Perform this exercise by standing with your feet placed together and arms at your sides. Now tuck in your abs and jump by bending in your knees. At the same time, move your feet apart as much as you can and raise your hands to bring in line with your shoulder. While you come back you must be in a starting position, feet together, hands at sides and knees bent. You must land on your heels and again jump. Jogging Jogging is one of the best home exercises witho...\n\nQ: To carry out home exercises continuously, you need  _  .", "options": ["a good atmosphere.", "a good coach.", "a dance teacher", "a good timer."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1520, "question": "Dear Ana, In your last letter, you told me that your boss Stephanie was probably looking for a new job and you didn't know how to tell her that you wanted to take her position if she left. Well, I'd like to tell you that there is no polite way to talk about this situation with your boss. After all, you are not one-hundred-percent sure that she is actually job-hunting. Even if you know for sure that she is, you can't, because it's not your business. Still, there are a couple of things that you can do to put yourself in a good position in case your boss does _ in the near future. First, you can have a general conversation with her about your career plans. Say something like, \"You've always been supportive of me, Stephanie, and I'd love you to give me some advice on my professional developmen...\n\nQ: We can infer that Ana's purpose for writing to Liz was to  _  .", "options": ["tell Liz that her boss is looking for a new job", "ask Liz if she has the ability to take her boss's position", "ask Liz for advice on how to find a much better job", "seek advice on how to make her boss know she wants her position"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 872, "question": "I must have been about fourteen then, and I put away the incident from my mind with the easy carelessness of youth. But the words, Carl Walter spoke that day, came back to me years later, and ever since have been of great value to me. Carl Walter was my piano teacher. During one of my lessons he asked how much practicing I was doing. I said three or four hours a day. \"Do you practice , an hour at a time?\" \"I try to.\" \"Well, don't,\" he exclaimed. \"When you grow up, time won't come in long stretches. Practice in minutes, whenever you can find them five or ten before school, after lunch, between household tasks. Spread the practice through the day, and piano-playing will become a part of your life.\" When I was teaching at Columbia, I wanted to write, but class periods, theme-reading, and comm...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["The writer didn't completely take the teacher's words to heart at first.", "Carl Walter has had a great influence on the writer's life since he became a student.", "The writer owes great thanks to his teacher for teaching him to work in long stretches.", "Rapid concentration is actually more difficult than most people imagine."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 942, "question": "It was near dusk, and Kim Cooper and her husband, Steve, were trucking through northern Kentucky transportation auto parts from Louisville to Detroit for a goods company. \"Steve, wake up!\" she shouted. \"There's a truck on fire!\" Inside the burning truck, Ronnie Sanders, 38, was fighting for his life. He'd been running a heavy load of tractors and forklifts from Georgia to Indianapolis when a van in front of him stopped suddenly in traffic on the icy road. As Ronnie bore down, he could see children in the backseat. The truck's bulk would probably protect him from the worst of the impact, but the force of 23 tons would likely crush everyone inside the van. \"I figured instead of killing other people, I'd just put the truck in the ditch.\" At the bottom, rocks cut a fuel tank, which caught fire...\n\nQ: What probably made Ronnie come to life after driving the truck in the ditch?", "options": ["The noise from the highway.", "The call from the Coopers.", "The pain from the burning legs.", "The heat of the fire."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1612, "question": "November not only marks the publication of Toni Morrison's eagerly anticipated eighth novel, Love, but it is also the tenth anniversary of her Nobel Prize for Literature. Morrison is the first black woman to receive a Nobel, and so honored before her in literature are only two black men:Wole Soyinka, the Nigerian playwright, poet and novelist, in 1986; and Derek Walcott, the Caribbean-born poet, in 1992. But Morrison is also the first and only American-born Nobel prizewinner for literature since 1962, the year novelist John Steinbeck received the award. Like Song of Solomon, Love is a multigenerational story, revealing the personal and communal Legacy of an outstanding black family. As Morrison scholars will tell you, Love is the third volume of a literary master's trilogy investigating th...\n\nQ: The similarity between Love and Song of Solomon is that they both   _  .", "options": ["belong to the same trilogy together with Beloved", "concern families of more than one generation", "deal with life of blacks under slavery", "investigate life in 1920s Harlem"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2785, "question": "There are two factors which determine an individual's intelligence. The first is the sort of brain he is born with. Human brains differ considerably, some being more capable than others. But no matter how good a brain he has to begin with, an individual will have a low order of intelligence unless he has opportunities to learn. So the second factor is what happens to the individual--the sort of environment in which he is reared . If an individual is handicapped environmentally, it is likely that his brain will fail to develop and he will never attain the level of intelligence of which he is capable. The importance of environment in determining an individual's intelligence can be demonstrated by the case history of the identical twins, Peter and Mark X. Being identical, the twins had identi...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the average I.Q. is   _  .", "options": ["85", "125", "110", "100"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2911, "question": "When I came to Cincinnati as an au pair , a lot of things there were different from what I knew. My host family lived in a huge house I could only describe as a \"castle\".In Germany I had lived in a small apartment together with my mom. Soon I found out that the \"castle\" was actually rather small in our neighborhood. Everybody there was very friendly and polite. They greeted you when they were walking by at least 3 feet away from you. They must not have seen a German au pair before, for most people I met asked me all kinds of questions about Germany. I enjoyed answering their various strange questions. I made a lot of friends and I started to hang out with them. Of course, there were a number of new things, and it took me the whole year to find them all out. I never got homesick. Perhaps it...\n\nQ: What is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["University life in Germany", "My culture shock experience", "Advantages of living in USA", "How to be an au pair in USA"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1798, "question": "By teaching your children fire safety you can make sure they know what to do when a house fire occurs. Making sure that your children know exactly what is required of them cuts down on the chaos of the emergency situation and helps keep your family safe and secure. Make sure your children know how to correctly stop, drop, and roll and feel confident in the fact that it works. It puts out the flames. The usual response to clothing catching on fire is to run around and run about wildly, which only exposes the fire to more oxygen and feeds the flames. Your children should also know to touch door handles before opening the door to see if they are hot. If they are, it means that there's a fire in the next room, and they should leave the door closed and find another route out of the house. Make ...\n\nQ: What should parents do with items like lighters and matches?", "options": ["Let them play with them.", "Hide them from the children.", "Experiment with them.", "Throw them out of the house."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1903, "question": "Students usually have two long holidays a year, but have you heard elephants have holidays? The Indian elephants from a temple are sent on a north-long holiday with massages and baths to relax. The 64 elephants will be fed with a lot of food, enough for them to put on 700~800 pounds. A temple veterinarian said that those Indian elephants would be treated after spending a month walking on roads, living on leaves and bananas and giving shows during lots of temple festivals. Their daily diet includes special rice and other special food, which are very _ and can make them healthy and strong. All of these are made by professional people. This treatment will also calm them down ahead of a busy work schedule in upcoming events later in the year where they are the main attractions. The special hol...\n\nQ: People give these elephants a special holiday in order to   _  .", "options": ["save a lot of money", "make friends with them", "make their temples famous", "make them get ready for the coming work."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 726, "question": "Expensive and new gloves allow chatterboxes to take the term \"handsfree\" to a new level--by talking into them as they make a call. The gloves are known as \"Talk to the Hand\" and cost PS1,000 a pair. They fixed a speaker unit into the thumb and a microphone into the little finger that can be connected to any mobile handset using Bluetooth. Artist Sean Miles designed the new gloves that double as a phone in part of his project that shows the possibilities of gadget(,) recycling. He uses outdated gloves and combines them with parts from mobile handsets recycled through _ , which commissioned the project. Mobile phone users will be able to keep their hands warm while they chat without taking their phones out of their pockets or handbags. Mr Miles designed two pairs of the new gloves--one in pi...\n\nQ: Consumers can buy the \"Talk to the Hand\" gloves   _  .", "options": ["in the exhibition", "from Mr Miles", "when they are mass produced", "after they recycle the gadgets"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1652, "question": "Do you love Beats headphones, True Religion jeans, and UGG shoes? These are some of the most popular brands around. They are also expensive. But some experts say they are not much better than cheaper brands. For example, Jim Wilcox works for Consumer Reports. He tested all kinds of headphones. He says that $80 Koss Pro headphones provide basically the same quality and comfort as Beats. So why do people pay twice or even 10 times as much for the hottest brands? Experts say it's because fashionable, expensive brands send a message. Brands say \"I belong\" or \"I can afford it.\" Some people think that expensive brand names are worth the price. They say that some designer clothes really are top quality and that they last longer than cheaper brands. Some teenagers choose to wear popular brands bec...\n\nQ: The example of Jim's report wants to tell us   _  .", "options": ["popular brands make people comfortable", "Koss Pro headphones are better than Beats", "the hottest brands are of the highest quality", "less-known brands may offer the same quality as name brands"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 211, "question": "On a small farm in Mexico, there are no schools. A bus is the school! The driver of the bus is the teacher! It is a school bus, but it doesn't take children to school. It just goes round from place to place, and sometimes it comes to this farm. The bus will stay here for three months. The farmers call it a school on wheels . Every time the bus comes, the farmers come running to it, shouting and laughing. They warmly welcome the school bus! When the bus is on the farm, in the morning, the teacher teaches the small children. In the afternoon, the bigger children come to have their lessons because they must work in the morning. At night, the fathers and mothers come to school. They want to learn, too. How the farmers hope that some day they can have a real school on their farm!...\n\nQ: .  . When the school bus comes, the farmers  are    _  .", "options": ["sad", "angry", "be happy", "disappointed"], "answer": 2}]